# Phạm Phái Hà

Front-end developer

0886323318

Ha Noi

# MY WEBSITE

https://www.phamha.info/

# **OBJECTIVE**

I'm currently a developer. I'm a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience. I has worked in the fields of software development, E-commerce, ERP, CRM and blockchain related projects. I is passionate about technology and cryptocurrency.

# **EDUCATION**

August - 2017 - 2021

#### **MAJOR:INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Transportation Technology University

4th year student

August - 2018 - 2021

#### **MAJOR: WEB FULL-STACK**

VTC Academy

Graduated

# SKILL

#### Devops:

Azure could service. github action, CICD, S3

#### Framework:

Reactjs, Nextjs, Vuejs, Angular (typescript)

#### **Blockchain:**

hardhat, ertherjs, web3js, metamask, sodility

#### UI:

Material ui, Antd, Bootstrap, Tailwild css, Storybook, SCSS

#### Oath2:

google, Microsoft, facebook

#### Manage:

Google Analytics

#### Base soure:

webpack, eslint, commint lint, babel

#### Realtime:

mqtt, firebase, socket

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Tekmate Software Solution**

12-2019 - 04-2020

# PROJECTNAME :XAYDUNG CO

Member: 9 (1 Tester, 6 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA)

Position: Intern

Project Description: Building web app for selling construction company's tools like Fiver.

Technology: React JS

Work Description: create UI/UX, work with BE dev and add api

### **GMO-Z.com Runsystem**

07-2020 - 12-2020

**PROJECTNAME: SALE FIE** 

Member: 12 (1 Tester, 8 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 QA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description: staffs management project, Technology Award 'Sao Khue 2021' of

vietnam.

Award Link: https://runsystem.net/vi/2021/04/26/gmo-z-com-runsystem-nhan-cu-dup-2-

danh-hieu-sao-khue-2021-cho-san-pham-chuyen-doi/

Technology: React JS

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api

Link: https://salefie.vn/

# **GMO-Z.com Runsystem**

12-2020 - 05-2021

### **PROJECTNAME: KAIKE**

Member: 11 (1 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 QA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description: website accounting project. Helping users who do not know about

accounting can also do a professional accountant

Technology: React JS (webpack)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api

Link: https://app.kaike.vn/

#### **GMO-Z.com Runsystem**

05-2021 - 07-2021

# **PROJECTNAME: ADMIN PL**

Member: 13 (3 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1 BA, 1 OA)

Position: ReactJs developer

Project Description :work time management

Technology: React JS (webpack)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project

front-end Link: private

#### **GMO-Z.com Runsystem**

07-2021 - 09-2021

# PROJECTNAME: MYSGR (ONSITE)

Member: 9 (1 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM)

Position: ReactJs developer, review code, tech lead Project Description: Staffs management off Sun Group

Technology: React JS (webpack), Node (ODDO)

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project

front-end, work with filebase, backend ODDO, review code, merge code

Link: private

#### **Filink**

11-2021 - 3-2022

# PROJECTNAME: LSTN (PRODUCT)

Member: (5 front-end)

Position: ReactJs developer, teamlead

Project Description: Auction of NFT products

Technology: React JS ,Web3js

Work Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev and add api, manage project front-end, call data from Blockchain. convert many money, connect metamask wallet

Link: https://listencampaign.com/listen\_campaign\_elements

#### **FPT** PROJECTNAME: AURA-SAFE(PRODUCT)

Member: (1 front-end)

Position: ReactJs developer,

3-2022 - End

Project Description: Look like gnosis safe, manager many wallet cryto

 $\label{thm:constraint} \textbf{Technology: React JS \ ,} \textbf{Web3jsWork Description: make UI/UX like a design, work with BE \ dev}$ 

and add api,call data form Blockchain. connect keplr, coin 98 wallet

Link: https://test.pyxis.aura.network/welcome

Link landing: https://pyxis.aura.network/

© topcv.vn